(Howard:)But don't you think it'll be
different when the child is ours?
(Bernadette:)Right. When it's our kid that's ruined
my body, kept me up all night...
...and I've got no career, no future,
nothing to be happy about for 20 years.
(Bernadette:)Sure, that'll be completely different.
(Howard:)Well, yeah.
(Sheldon:)I don't think there's anything
in this jewelry store...
(Sheldon:)...that Amy would appreciate more than
the humidifier we're looking at at Sears.
(Penny:)Oh, my God. Now I know what I sound
Iike to you when I say stupid stuff.
Ooh! A pocket watch.
(Penny:)I don't think Amy
wants a pocket watch.
(Sheldon:)No, but maybe she wants
a man with a pocket watch.
(Penny:)Still saying stupid stuff.
(Penny:)- Does she like bracelets?
- Well, she's very fond of her silver one...